<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hackathons on WWCode ATX</title>
    <link>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hackathons on WWCode ATX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;Women Who Code ATX 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 13:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>6th ATX Diversity Hackathon Rules and Judging criteria</title>
      <link>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/hackathon-rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/hackathon-rules/</guid>
      <description>Prize Categories There are the five categories for prizes. All projects are automatically entered into all categories.
 Deep learning - Sponsored by Bestow UI/UX - Sponsored by The Zebra Social impact - Sponsored by Athena Health Technical stack - Sponsored by Athena Health Overall - Sponsored by Athena Health  Assembling Your Team The max team size is 5 people. You can organize your own team. If you are looking for projects or teammates, please sign up for slack here and use the #pitch channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6th ATX Diversity Hackathon Workshop Schedule</title>
      <link>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/workshops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/workshops/</guid>
      <description>FRIDAY, September 18 11:00 - 12:00 PM: Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion can&amp;rsquo;t be just terms that we use at work Presenter: Briona Jenkins [twitter instagram]
Visit Briona&amp;rsquo;s press page to listen to the panels and podcast, and the blog posts.
12:00 - 1:00 PM: How to Not Die Broke: Investing Strategies You Need to Know Presenter: Kara Perez [twitter instagram]
1:00 - 2:00 PM: Communicating with Diagrams: A designer&amp;rsquo;s tips for creating engineering diagrams that clearly &amp;amp; efficiently convey their intended message Presenter: Sara Wells</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Who Code Austin 6th Annual Diversity Hackathon Sign up</title>
      <link>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/signup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://WWCodeATX.github.io/hackathon/signup/</guid>
      <description>Join Women Who Code Austin (ATX) for our 6th annual Diversity Hackathon, sponsored by Google Fiber, Athena Health, Bestow and the Zebra. This is a virtual hackathon, with online workshops.
When: Fri, Sep 18, 2020, 9:00 AM – Sun, Sep 20, 2020, 5:00 PM CDT
Registration: sign up here
This hackathon is a celebration of diversity. Anyone who supports diversity is welcome — no matter your level of technical knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>